MAN WITH A MOVIE CAMERA
A record on celluloid in six reels.
Produced by VUFKU in 1929
(An excerpt from the diary of a cameraman).
For the attention of the spectator:
This film presents an experiment
in the cinematic transmission
of visible phenomena.
Without the aid of intertitles
(a film without intertitles)
Without the aid of a script
(a film without a script)
Without the aid of theatre
(a film without sets, actors, etc.)
This experimental work aims at creating
a truly international absolute language
of cinema based on
its total separation
from the language of
theatre and literature.
Author-supervisor of the experiment
DZIGA VERTOV
Chief cameraman
MIKHAIL KAUFMAN
Assistant editor
ELIZAVETA SVILOVA
THE END